Library of American Broadcasting Scripts collection
University of Maryland Libraries
- Radio and television Scripts, 1925-1991; 723 items
  - National Barn Dance -- The Dizz Kids, 9/11/1948 (Folder 105.0)
    - National Barn Dance, 9/18/1948 (Item null)
  - National Barn Dance -- The Dizz Kids, 9/18/1948 (Folder 106.0)
    - National Barn Dance, 10/2/1948 (Item null)
  - National Barn Dance -- The Dizz Kids, 10/2/1948 (Folder 107.0)
    - National Barn Dance, 10/9/1948 (Item null)
  - National Barn Dance -- The Dizz Kids, 10/9/1948 (Folder 108.0)
    - National Barn Dance, 10/16/1948 (Item null)
  - National Barn Dance -- The Dizz Kids, 10/16/1948 (Folder 109.0)
    - National Barn Dance, 10/23/1948 (Item null)
  - National Barn Dance -- The Dizz Kids, 10/23/1948 (Folder 110.0)
    - National Barn Dance, 12/18/1948 (Item null)
  - National Barn Dance -- The Dizz Kids, 12/18/1948 (Folder 111.0)
    - National Barn Dance, 1/1/1949 (Item null)
  - National Barn Dance -- The Dizz Kids, 1/1/1949 (Folder 112.0)
    - National Barn Dance, 1/8/1949 (Item null)
  - National Barn Dance, 1/8/1949 (Folder 113.0)
    - National Barn Dance, 8/16/1952 (Item null)
  - National Barn Dance, 8/16/1952 (Folder 114.0)
    - National Barn Dance, 9/6/1952 (Item null)
  - National Barn Dance, 9/6/1952 (Folder 115.0)
    - National Barn Dance, 10/11/1952 (Item null)
  - National Barn Dance, 10/11/1952 (Folder 116.0)
    - National Polling Day: The Surprising Americans, 4/16/1971 (Item null)
  - National Polling Day: The Surprising Americans, 4/16/1971 (Folder 117.0)
    - NBC Jamboree, null (Item null)
  - NBC Jamboree (Folder 118.0)
    - NBC Jamboree, 8/16/1938 (Item null)
  - NBC Jamboree, 8/16/1938 (Folder 119.0)
    - NBC Jamboree, 8/23/1938 (Item null)
  - NBC Jamboree, 8/23/1938 (Folder 120.0)
    - NBC Jamboree, 9/6/1938 (Item null)
  - NBC Jamboree -- On a Farm, 9/6/1938 (Folder 121.0)
    - NBC Minstrels of 1938, 7/6/1938 (Item null)
  - NBC Minstrels of 1938 -- Dream Show, 7/6/1938 (Folder 122.0)
    - NBC Minstrels of 1938, 7/25/1938 (Item null)
  - NBC Minstrels of 1938 -- Russia in the Mediterranean, 7/25/1938 (Folder 123.0)
    - NBC News Special, 3/16/1969 (Item null)
  - NBC News Special, 3/16/1969 (Folder 124.0)
    - Nickelodeon, 2/4/1936 (Item null)
  - Nickelodeon, 2/4/1936 (Folder 125.0)
    - Once Upon a World, 3/8/1970 (Item null)
  - Once Upon a World, 3/8/1970 (Folder 126.0)
    - One Man's Family, 4/29/1932 (Item null)
  - One Man's Family -- Private Secretaries and Saxaphones, 4/29/1932 (Folder 127.0)
    - One Man's Family, 6/17/1932 (Item null)
  - One Man's Family, 6/17/1932 (Folder 128.0)
    - Orson Welles Show, 6/21/1944 (Item null)
  - Orson Welles Show, 6/21/1944 (Folder 129.0)
    - Pat Butram - Jack Murphy Routine, 5/18/1946 (Item null)
  - Pat Butram - Jack Murphy Routine, 5/18/1946 (Folder 130.0)
    - Pat Butram - Jack Murphy Routine, 5/25/1946 (Item null)
  - Pat Butram - Jack Murphy Routine, 5/25/1946 (Folder 131.0)
    - Patterson Savings Institution Memoires, 1/1/1942 (Item null)
  - Patterson Savings Institution Memoires, 1/1/1942 (Folder 132.0)
    - Pee Wee Reese Show, The, 4/16/1952 (Item null)
  - Pee Wee Reese Show, The, 4/16/1952 (Folder 133.0)
    - Pee Wee Reese Show, The, 4/26/1952 (Item null)
  - Pee Wee Reese Show, The, 4/26/1952 (Folder 134.0)
    - Pee Wee Reese Show, The, 5/10/1952 (Item null)
  - Pee Wee Reese Show, The, 5/10/1952 (Folder 135.0)
    - Pee Wee Reese Show, The, 5/31/1952 (Item null)
  - Pee Wee Reese Show, The, 5/31/1952 (Folder 136.0)
    - Pee Wee Reese Show, The, 6/7/1952 (Item null)
  - Pee Wee Reese Show, The, 6/7/1952 (Folder 137.0)
    - Pee Wee Reese Show, The, 6/14/1952 (Item null)
  - Pee Wee Reese Show, The, 6/14/1952 (Folder 138.0)
    - Pee Wee Reese Show, The, 6/28/1952 (Item null)
  - Pee Wee Reese Show, The, 6/28/1952 (Folder 139.0)
    - Pee Wee Reese Show, The, 7/5/1952 (Item null)
  - Pee Wee Reese Show, The, 7/5/1952 (Folder 140.0)
    - People I Have Known, 8/18/1938 (Item null)
  - People I Have Known, 8/18/1938 (Folder 141.0)
    - People I Have Known, 9/8/1938 (Item null)
  - Play is the Thing, The -- The Apple Tree (Box 5, Folder 1.0)
    - Play is the Thing, The, 3/3/1950 (Item null)
  - Play is the Thing, The -- The Salt of the Earth, 3/3/1950 (Folder 2.0)
    - Play is the Thing, The, 3/31/1950 (Item null)
  - Play is the Thing, The -- Sanctuary in Paris, 3/31/1950 (Folder 3.0)
    - Play is the Thing, The, 4/14/1950 (Item null)
  - Play is the Thing, The, 4/14/1950 (Folder 4.0)
    - Prairie Farmer, 2/9/1946 (Item null)
  - Prairie Farmer, 2/9/1946 (Folder 5.0)
    - Prairie Farmer, 10/21/1946 (Item null)
  - Prairie Farmer -- Adventures in Health, 10/21/1946 (Folder 6.0)
    - Prairie Farmer, 10/28/1946 (Item null)
  - Prairie Farmer, 10/28/1946 (Folder 7.0)
    - Princess Pat- A Tale of Today, 7/3/1938 (Item null)
  - Princess Pat- A Tale of Today, 7/3/1938 (Folder 8.0)
    - Princess Pat- A Tale of Today, 7/10/1938 (Item null)
  - Princess Pat- A Tale of Today, 7/10/1938 (Folder 9.0)
    - Public Hero Number One, 7/4/1938 (Item null)
  - Public Hero Number One, 7/4/1938 (Folder 10.0)
    - Public Hero Number One, 7/11/1938 (Item null)
  - Public Hero Number One, 7/11/1938 (Folder 11.0)
    - Public Hero Number One, 7/24/1938 (Item null)
  - Public Hero Number One, 7/24/1938 (Folder 12.0)
    - Public Hero Number One, 7/25/1938 (Item null)
  - Public Hero Number One, 7/25/1938 (Folder 13.0)
    - Purbump, 8/2/1944 (Item null)
  - Purbump -- How to Place and Build People, 8/2/1944 (Folder 14.0)
    - Pursuit of Happiness, The, 7/14/1944 (Item null)
  - Pursuit of Happiness, The -- Attack the Problem, 7/14/1944 (Folder 15.0)
    - Pursuit of Happiness, The, 8/1/1944 (Item null)
  - Pursuit of Happiness, The, 8/1/1944 (Folder 16.0)
    - Radio: A Broadcast Novelty, 1/1/1926 (Item null)
  - Radio: A Broadcast Novelty, 1/1/1926 (Folder 17.0)
    - Romeo and Juliet, null (Item null)
  - Romeo and Juliet (Folder 18.0)
    - Salerno Question-Air, 2/20/1938 (Item null)
  - Salerno Question-Air, 2/20/1938 (Folder 19.0)
    - Salerno Question-Air, 5/8/1938 (Item null)
  - Salerno Question-Air, 5/8/1938 (Folder 20.0)
    - Salerno Question-Air, 7/3/1938 (Item null)
  - Salerno Question-Air, 7/3/1938 (Folder 21.0)
    - Salerno Question-Air, 7/10/1938 (Item null)
  - Salerno Question-Air, 7/10/1938 (Folder 22.0)
    - Salerno Question-Air, 8/28/1938 (Item null)
  - Salerno Question-Air, 8/28/1938 (Folder 23.0)
    - Salerno Question-Air, 9/4/1938 (Item null)
  - Salerno Question-Air, 9/4/1938 (Folder 24.0)
    - Salerno Question-Air, 9/11/1938 (Item null)
  - Salerno Question-Air, 9/11/1938 (Folder 25.0)
    - School Radio Scripts, 4/1/1939 (Item null)
  - School Radio Scripts, 4/1/1939 (Folder 26.0)
    - School Time Fill In, 12/27/1946 (Item null)
  - School Time Fill In, 12/27/1946 (Folder 27.0)
    - Scripts From Old Radio Shows, null (Item null)
  - Scripts From Old Radio Shows (Folder 28.0)
    - Show Boat, 5/10/1940 (Item null)
  - Show Boat, 5/10/1940 (Folder 29.0)
    - Show Boat, 6/4/1940 (Item null)
  - Show Boat, 6/4/1940 (Folder 30.0)
    - Show Boat, 6/21/1940 (Item null)
  - Show Boat, 6/21/1940 (Folder 31.0)
    - Show Boat, 6/28/1940 (Item null)
  - Show Boat, 6/28/1940 (Folder 32.0)
    - Show Boat, 7/19/1940 (Item null)
  - Show Boat, 7/19/1940 (Folder 33.0)
    - Show Boat, 8/5/1940 (Item null)
  - Show Boat, 8/5/1940 (Folder 34.0)
    - Show Boat, 8/12/1940 (Item null)
  - Show Boat, 8/12/1940 (Folder 35.0)
    - Show Boat, 9/16/1940 (Item null)
  - Show Boat, 9/16/1940 (Folder 36.0)
    - Show Boat, 9/23/1940 (Item null)
  - Show Boat, 9/23/1940 (Folder 37.0)
    - Show Boat, 10/7/1940 (Item null)
  - Show Boat, 10/7/1940 (Folder 38.0)
    - Sinclair Minstrels, 12/18/1933 (Item null)
  - Sinclair Minstrels, 12/18/1933 (Folder 39.0)
    - Sinclair Minstrels, 1/8/1934 (Item null)
  - Sinclair Minstrels, 1/8/1934 (Folder 40.0)
    - Sinclair Minstrels, 2/25/1935 (Item null)
  - Sinclair Minstrels -- Danger on the Roaring River, 2/25/1935 (Folder 41.0)
    - Sky King, null (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Battle for Oil (Folder 42.0)
    - Sky King, null (Item null)
  - Sky King (Folder 43.0)
    - Sky King, 8/22/1947 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Mystery of the Vanishing Pearls, 8/22/1947 (Folder 44.0)
    - Sky King, 6/10/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Mystery on Mesa Blanca, 6/10/1948 (Folder 45.0)
    - Sky King, 6/18/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Rainmakers Magic, 6/18/1948 (Folder 46.0)
    - Sky King, 6/28/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Danger Rides at the Rodeo, 6/28/1948 (Folder 47.0)
    - Sky King, 7/8/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Lobster Claw, 7/8/1948 (Folder 48.0)
    - Sky King, 7/16/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Search for the Teakwood Chest, 7/16/1948 (Folder 49.0)
    - Sky King, 7/22/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Blue Steak Across the Border, 7/22/1948 (Folder 50.0)
    - Sky King, 8/3/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Disaster Walks Underground, 8/3/1948 (Folder 51.0)
    - Sky King, 8/17/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Destruction on Wheels, 8/17/1948 (Folder 52.0)
    - Sky King, 8/23/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Mystery Under Roaring River, 8/23/1948 (Folder 53.0)
    - Sky King, 8/31/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Man Hunt in Skull Creek Valley, 8/31/1948 (Folder 54.0)
    - Sky King, 9/7/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Peril on the Highline, 9/7/1948 (Folder 55.0)
    - Sky King, 9/13/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Medical Mission to Devil's Mesa, 9/13/1948 (Folder 56.0)
    - Sky King, 9/17/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Man with the Bamboo Cane, 9/17/1948 (Folder 57.0)
    - Sky King, 9/23/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Clue, 9/23/1948 (Folder 58.0)
    - Sky King, 9/30/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Meeting at Midnight, 9/30/1948 (Folder 59.0)
    - Sky King, 10/7/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Disaster Canyon, 10/7/1948 (Folder 60.0)
    - Sky King, 10/19/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Post Card Heiress, 10/19/1948 (Folder 61.0)
    - Sky King, 10/25/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Nine Perilous Flights, 10/25/1948 (Folder 62.0)
    - Sky King, 11/1/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Final Clue, 11/1/1948 (Folder 63.0)
    - Sky King, 11/22/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Dead Ringer, 11/22/1948 (Folder 64.0)
    - Sky King, 11/30/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Battle at Sawmill, 11/30/1948 (Folder 65.0)
    - Sky King, 12/6/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Riddle of the Lost Loot, 12/6/1948 (Folder 66.0)
    - Sky King, 12/14/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Ambush in Miracle Pass, 12/14/1948 (Folder 67.0)
    - Sky King, 12/20/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Battle of the Twenty Ton Cats, 12/20/1948 (Folder 68.0)
    - Sky King, 12/28/1948 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Evidence in Wax, 12/28/1948 (Folder 69.0)
    - Sky King, 1/3/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Listener, 1/3/1949 (Folder 70.0)
    - Sky King, 1/11/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Attack with the Silent Gun, 1/11/1949 (Folder 71.0)
    - Sky King, 1/21/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Nine Secret Steps, 1/21/1949 (Folder 72.0)
    - Sky King, 1/24/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Tree House People, 1/24/1949 (Folder 73.0)
    - Sky King, 1/31/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Fires of Ogalar, 1/31/1949 (Folder 74.0)
    - Sky King, 2/7/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Laughing Bandit, 2/7/1949 (Folder 75.0)
    - Sky King, 2/14/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Tiger Clawed Gang, 2/14/1949 (Folder 76.0)
    - Sky King, 2/22/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Showdown in Phantom Canyon, 2/22/1949 (Folder 77.0)
    - Sky King, 3/8/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Comet Racer, 3/8/1949 (Folder 78.0)
    - Sky King, 3/15/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Weaver's Ghost, 3/15/1949 (Folder 79.0)
    - Sky King, 3/24/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Four Point Star, 3/24/1949 (Folder 80.0)
    - Sky King, 3/31/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Peril on the Border, 3/31/1949 (Folder 81.0)
    - Sky King, 4/8/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Man From Shark Tooth Key, 4/8/1949 (Folder 82.0)
    - Sky King, 4/15/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Leap for Life, 4/15/1949 (Folder 83.0)
    - Sky King, 4/22/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Whistling Theif, 4/22/1949 (Folder 84.0)
    - Sky King, 4/28/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Fire Under Water, 4/28/1949 (Folder 85.0)
    - Sky King, 5/16/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- My Memory Forgerts, 5/16/1949 (Folder 86.0)
    - Sky King, 5/24/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Phantom Highjacker, 5/24/1949 (Folder 87.0)
    - Sky King, 6/16/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Highline Flyer, 6/16/1949 (Folder 88.0)
    - Sky King, 7/26/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- Peril Rides the Cattle Train, 7/26/1949 (Folder 89.0)
    - Sky King, 8/4/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Mystery Clouds, 8/4/1949 (Folder 90.0)
    - Sky King, 8/11/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Puzzle in a Blue Envelope, 8/11/1949 (Folder 91.0)
    - Sky King, 8/23/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Whip, 8/23/1949 (Folder 92.0)
    - Sky King, 8/30/1949 (Item null)
  - Sky King -- The Night Raiders, 8/30/1949 (Folder 93.0)
    - Sky King, 5/31/1950 (Item null)
  - Sky King, 5/31/1950 (Folder 94.0)
    - Sky's the Limit, The, 3/28/1942 (Item null)
  - People I Have Known, 9/8/1938 (Folder 142.0)
  - Personalities at 711, 12/13/1929 (Folder 143.0)
    - Play is the Thing, The, null (Item null)
  - Sky's the Limit, The -- miscellaneous, 3/7/1943 (Box 6, Folder 1.0)
    - Soconyland Sketches, null (Item null)
  - Soconyland Sketches -- The Melting Pot of '77 (Folder 2.0)
    - Soconyland Sketches, 6/24/1930 (Item null)
  - Soconyland Sketches -- O Deer, 6/24/1930 (Folder 3.0)
    - Soconyland Sketches, 12/9/1930 (Item null)
  - Soconyland Sketches -- The Tale of a Wayside Stand, 12/9/1930 (Folder 4.0)
    - Soconyland Sketches, 7/14/1931 (Item null)
  - Soconyland Sketches -- Sebago Lake, 7/14/1931 (Folder 5.0)
    - Soconyland Sketches, 4/11/1932 (Item null)
  - Soconyland Sketches -- The Flag, 4/11/1932 (Folder 6.0)
    - Soconyland Sketches, 6/13/1932 (Item null)
  - Soconyland Sketches -- Old Bet, 6/13/1932 (Folder 7.0)
    - Soconyland Sketches, 5/7/1934 (Item null)
  - Soconyland Sketches, 5/7/1934 (Folder 8.0)
    - Soldier Shows Script, 4/1/1952 (Item null)
  - Soldier Shows Script, 4/1/1952 (Folder 9.0)
    - Soldier Shows Script, 8/1/1952 (Item null)
  - Soldier Shows Script, 8/1/1952 (Folder 10.0)
    - Soldier Shows Script, 12/1/1954 (Item null)
  - Soldier Shows Script, 12/1/1954 (Folder 11.0)
    - Stebbins Boys, The, null (Item null)
  - Stebbins Boys, The (Folder 12.0)
    - Stebbins Boys, The, null (Item null)
  - Stebbins Boys, The (Folder 13.0)
    - Stebbins Boys, The, null (Item null)
  - Stebbins Boys, The (Folder 14.0)
    - Stebbins Boys, The, null (Item null)
  - Stebbins Boys, The (Folder 15.0)
    - Stebbins Boys, The, null (Item null)
  - Stebbins Boys, The (Folder 16.0)
    - Stebbins Boys, The, null (Item null)
  - Stebbins Boys, The (Folder 17.0)
    - Stebbins Boys, The, null (Item null)
  - Stebbins Boys, The (Folder 18.0)
    - Stebbins Boys, The, null (Item null)
  - Stebbins Boys, The (Folder 19.0)
    - Stebbins Boys, The, null (Item null)
  - Stebbins Boys, The (Folder 20.0)
    - Stebbins Boys, The, null (Item null)
  - Stebbins Boys, The (Folder 21.0)
    - Stebbins Boys, The, null (Item null)
  - Stebbins Boys, The -- Death (Folder 22.0)
    - Suspense TV, 7/27/1954 (Item null)
  - Suspense TV -- Audition, 7/27/1954 (Folder 23.0)
    - Swop Night, 11/6/1941 (Item null)
  - Swop Night, 11/6/1941 (Folder 24.0)
    - Swop Nite, 2/14/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 2/14/1942 (Folder 25.0)
    - Swop Nite, 2/21/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 2/21/1942 (Folder 26.0)
    - Swop Nite, 2/28/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 2/28/1942 (Folder 27.0)
    - Swop Nite, 3/7/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 3/7/1942 (Folder 28.0)
    - Swop NIte, 3/17/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop NIte, 3/17/1942 (Folder 29.0)
    - Swop Nite, 3/21/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 3/21/1942 (Folder 30.0)
    - Swop Nite, 3/28/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 3/28/1942 (Folder 31.0)
    - Swop Nite, 4/4/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 4/4/1942 (Folder 32.0)
    - Swop Nite, 4/11/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 4/11/1942 (Folder 33.0)
    - Swop Nite, 4/18/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 4/18/1942 (Folder 34.0)
    - Swop Nite, 4/25/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 4/25/1942 (Folder 35.0)
    - Swop Nite, 5/9/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 5/9/1942 (Folder 36.0)
    - Swop Nite, 5/16/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 5/16/1942 (Folder 37.0)
    - Swop Nite, 5/30/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 5/30/1942 (Folder 38.0)
    - Swop Nite, 6/6/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 6/6/1942 (Folder 39.0)
    - Swop Nite, 6/13/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 6/13/1942 (Folder 40.0)
    - Swop Nite, 6/20/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 6/20/1942 (Folder 41.0)
    - Swop Nite, 6/27/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 6/27/1942 (Folder 42.0)
    - Swop Nite, 7/4/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 7/4/1942 (Folder 43.0)
    - Swop Nite, 7/11/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 7/11/1942 (Folder 44.0)
    - Swop Nite, 7/18/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 7/18/1942 (Folder 45.0)
    - Swop NIte, 7/25/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop NIte, 7/25/1942 (Folder 46.0)
    - Swop Nite, 8/1/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 8/1/1942 (Folder 47.0)
    - Swop Nite, 8/8/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 8/8/1942 (Folder 48.0)
    - Swop Nite, 8/15/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 8/15/1942 (Folder 49.0)
    - Swop Nite, 8/22/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 8/22/1942 (Folder 50.0)
    - Swop Nite, 8/29/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 8/29/1942 (Folder 51.0)
    - Swop Nite, 9/5/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 9/5/1942 (Folder 52.0)
    - Swop Nite, 9/12/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 9/12/1942 (Folder 53.0)
    - Swop Nite, 9/19/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 9/19/1942 (Folder 54.0)
    - Swop Nite, 9/26/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 9/26/1942 (Folder 55.0)
    - Swop Nite, 10/24/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite, 10/24/1942 (Folder 56.0)
    - Swop Nite, 10/31/1942 (Item null)
  - Swop Nite -- The Weak Spot, 10/31/1942 (Folder 57.0)
    - Tele-Theatre, 3/27/1946 (Item null)
  - Tele-Theatre -- The Story of Sarah Todd Astor, 3/27/1946 (Folder 58.0)
    - There Was a Woman, 1/2/1937 (Item null)
  - There Was a Woman -- The Story of Eliza Allen, 1/2/1937 (Folder 59.0)
    - There Was a Woman, 11/14/1937 (Item null)
  - There Was a Woman -- The Story of Marie Villars Lafitte, 11/14/1937 (Folder 60.0)
    - There Was a Woman, 11/28/1937 (Item null)
  - There Was a Woman -- The Story of Margaret Maskelyne Clive, 11/28/1937 (Folder 61.0)
    - There Was a Woman, 12/5/1937 (Item null)
  - There Was a Woman -- The Story of Alexandra, Czarina of Russia, 12/5/1937 (Folder 62.0)
    - There Was a Woman, 12/19/1937 (Item null)
  - Sky's the Limit, The, 3/28/1942 (Folder 95.0)
  - Sky's the Limit, The, 2/28/1943 (Folder 96.0)
    - Sky's the Limit, The, 3/7/1943 (Item null)
  - There Was a Woman, 9/4/1938 (Box 7, Folder 1.0)
    - This is New York, 1/22/1939 (Item null)
  - This is New York, 1/22/1939 (Folder 2.0)
    - This is Your FBI, 7/26/1946 (Item null)
  - This is Your FBI -- audition, 7/26/1946 (Folder 3.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 1/1/1941 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 1/1/1941 (Folder 4.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 10/5/1941 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 10/5/1941 (Folder 5.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 10/12/1941 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 10/12/1941 (Folder 6.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 10/19/1941 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 10/19/1941 (Folder 7.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 10/26/1941 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 10/26/1941 (Folder 8.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 11/2/1941 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 11/2/1941 (Folder 9.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 11/9/1941 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 11/9/1941 (Folder 10.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 11/16/1941 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 11/16/1941 (Folder 11.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 11/23/1941 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 11/23/1941 (Folder 12.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 12/7/1941 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 12/7/1941 (Folder 13.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 12/14/1941 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 12/14/1941 (Folder 14.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 12/21/1941 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 12/21/1941 (Folder 15.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 12/28/1941 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 12/28/1941 (Folder 16.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 1/4/1942 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 1/4/1942 (Folder 17.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 1/11/1942 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 1/11/1942 (Folder 18.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 1/18/1942 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 1/18/1942 (Folder 19.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 1/25/1942 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 1/25/1942 (Folder 20.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 2/1/1942 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 2/1/1942 (Folder 21.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 2/8/1942 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 2/8/1942 (Folder 22.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 2/15/1942 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 2/15/1942 (Folder 23.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 2/22/1942 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 2/22/1942 (Folder 24.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 3/1/1942 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 3/1/1942 (Folder 25.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 3/8/1942 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 3/8/1942 (Folder 26.0)
    - Timid Soul, The, 3/15/1942 (Item null)
  - Timid Soul, The, 3/15/1942 (Folder 27.0)
    - Today's Children, 11/9/1937 (Item null)
  - Today's Children, 11/9/1937 (Folder 28.0)
    - Tribute to Frankin D. Roosevelt, 4/12/1945 (Item null)
  - Tribute to Frankin D. Roosevelt, 4/12/1945 (Folder 29.0)
    - True Story Magazine Presents I'll Never Forget, null (Item null)
  - True Story Magazine Presents I'll Never Forget (Folder 30.0)
    - Uncle Ezra- Station E.Z.R.A., 12/17/1937 (Item null)
  - Uncle Ezra- Station E.Z.R.A., 12/17/1937 (Folder 31.0)
    - Uncle Ezra- Station E.Z.R.A., 12/24/1937 (Item null)
  - Uncle Ezra- Station E.Z.R.A., 12/24/1937 (Folder 32.0)
    - Uncle Ezra- Station E.Z.R.A., 7/1/1938 (Item null)
  - Uncle Ezra- Station E.Z.R.A., 7/1/1938 (Folder 33.0)
    - Uncle Ezra- Station E.Z.R.A., 7/6/1938 (Item null)
  - Uncle Ezra- Station E.Z.R.A., 7/6/1938 (Folder 34.0)
    - Uncle Ezra- Station E.Z.R.A., 7/11/1938 (Item null)
  - Uncle Ezra- Station E.Z.R.A., 7/11/1938 (Folder 35.0)
    - Uncle Ezra- Station E.Z.R.A., 7/22/1938 (Item null)
  - Uncle Ezra- Station E.Z.R.A., 7/22/1938 (Folder 36.0)
    - Uncle Ezra- Station E.Z.R.A., 8/12/1938 (Item null)
  - Uncle Ezra- Station E.Z.R.A., 8/12/1938 (Folder 37.0)
    - Uncle Walter's Cut-up College, 6/14/1940 (Item null)
  - Uncle Walter's Cut-up College, 6/14/1940 (Folder 38.0)
    - Uncle Walter's Dog House, 6/25/1940 (Item null)
  - Uncle Walter's Dog House, 6/25/1940 (Folder 39.0)
    - Uncle Walter's Dog House, 7/23/1940 (Item null)
  - Uncle Walter's Dog House, 7/23/1940 (Folder 40.0)
    - Uncle Walter's Dog House, 7/30/1940 (Item null)
  - Uncle Walter's Dog House, 7/30/1940 (Folder 41.0)
    - Uncle Walter's Dog House, 8/6/1940 (Item null)
  - Uncle Walter's Dog House, 8/6/1940 (Folder 42.0)
    - Uncle Walter's Dog House, 8/13/1940 (Item null)
  - Uncle Walter's Dog House, 8/13/1940 (Folder 43.0)
    - Uncle Walter's Dog House, 9/24/1940 (Item null)
  - Uncle Walter's Dog House, 9/24/1940 (Folder 44.0)
    - Uncle Walter's Dog House, 12/3/1940 (Item null)
  - Uncle Walter's Dog House, 12/3/1940 (Folder 45.0)
    - Uncle Walter's Dog House, 1/28/1941 (Item null)
  - Uncle Walter's Dog House -- The Miner Fury, 1/28/1941 (Folder 46.0)
    - United Nations Educational Series, 2/9/1951 (Item null)
  - United Nations Educational Series, 2/9/1951 (Folder 47.0)
    - Veterans Jamboree, null (Item null)
  - Veterans Jamboree (Folder 48.0)
    - Vic and Sade, 7/5/1938 (Item null)